Guide to the Donald Kennedy Personal Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2009-139
  - Chang-Lin Tien Inauguration-UC Berkeley 3/22/91 (#444) (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - LA Alumni Conference – Remarks 3/23/91 (#445) (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Welcome – WIPO Symposium on Artificial Intelligence 3/25/91 (#446) (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - New York Alumni – Remarks (NYC) 3/27/91 (#447) (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Jordan Prize Presentation (notes) 4/4/91 (#448) (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Message to Faculty (Indirect Costs) – Academic Senate 4/4/91 (#449) (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Welcome - Health Policy/Pre-Natal Care (notes) Stanford Health Policy Forum 4/6/91 (#450) (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Remarks to Law School Faculty – IDC 4/29/91 (#451) (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Career Planning & Placement Center CPPR (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Panel on Teaching – Academic Council 5/2/91 (#452) (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - American law Institute Remarks 5/17/91 (#454) (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Hate Speech & Hate Thought Police – Panel 1st Amendment Challenges Commun. Dep't. 5/6/91 (#453) (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - University/Industry Nexus – CEPR Paul David Seminar 5/20/91 (#455) (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - State of the University (notes) South Bay Alumni-San Jose 5/21/91 (#456) (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Commencement 1991 Welcome 6/16/91 (#457A) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Introduction to John Gardner 6/16/91 (#457C) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Farewell to Graduates – Commencement '91 (#457B) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - John Gardner Speech – Commencement, (#457D) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Brock – Baccalaureate "Messages from my Grandmothers" (#457E) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Hoover Institution 50th Anniversary 7/18/91 (#458) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees Resignation 7/28/91 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Revised Mission Statement 9/1991 (#458A) (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Parents Day Convocation 1991 9/19/91 (#459) (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Welcome to Freshmen 9/20/91 (#460) (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Junior Convocation/Hoagland Award 9/26/91 see also #347 (#461) (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Gilbert Building Dedication 9/26/91 (#462) (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Centennial Weekend – Alumni Welcome/Bowman Grove 9/27/91 (#463) (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Centennial Talk – Kennedy (#464C) (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Welcome, Intro of Gov. Wilson (#464A,B) (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Gaither Remarks, Gov. Wilson Centennial Address (#464D,E) (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Mills College Inauguration 10/10/91 (#465) (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - ACE/NIP Welcome Remarks 10/24/91 (#466) (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Social and Political Challenges to Higher Education and Beyond 10/29/91 (#467) (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Social & Political Challenges to HiEd & Beyond – CalTech Conference 10/29/91 (#467) (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Centennial Wrap-up – SU Volunteers 2/9/92 (#468) (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - MIT Faculty Workshop – Public View of University Science? 3/10/92 (#469) (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Sons-in-retirement (notes) 3/18/92 (#470) (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Education in a World without Borders - Geneva 3/28/92 (#471) (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Education in a World without Borders – Geneva 4/1/92 (#472) (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Report to the Academic Council 4/30/92 (#472) (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Gorbachev Welcome 5/9/92 (#473) (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Address to Medical Staff 5/26/92 (#474) (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - SLE Remarks – SLE Banquet 6/3/92 (#475) (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Final Report to the BoT 6/12/92 (#476) (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Class Day Remarks "You Had To Be There" 6/13/92 (#476) (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Commencement Welcome Remarks 6/14/92 (#478A) (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Farewell to Class of '92 6/14/92 (#478B) (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Introduction of Kirk Varnedoe 6/14/92 (#478C) (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - K. Varnedoe's Commencement Address 6/14/92 (#478D) (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Introduction of David Kessler – Med School Graduation 6/14/92 (#479) (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Sierra Club (notes only) 7/9/92 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Report to the Hoover Board 7/23/92 (#480) (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - College of the Atlantic – "Environmental Challenge" 8/5/92 (#481) (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Young Alumni College 8/9/92 (#482) (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Winding Your Way Through DNA 9/25-9/26/92 (#483) (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Centennial Green Dedication 10/1/92 (#484) (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Casper Inauguration 10/2/92 (#485) (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Carnegie Commission in NY 10/1992 (#486) (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - ASTRO, San Diego – "Doing Better, Feeling Worse" 11/13/92 (#487) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Univ & Technology Dev: The Changing Role BA Biosci 11/18/92 (#488) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Gaither Appreciation 12/7/92 (#489) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Commencement (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - CNPA Some Thoughts from the Sullivan Side 2/13/93 (#490) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Partners Lunch – Covington & Burling 3/15/93 (#491) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Ethics Lectures 4/8 & 4/15/93 (#492) (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Health Library Panel 4/12/93 (#493) (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Borison Lecture (Dartmouth) 5/3/93 (#496) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Western Journal of Medecine May 21, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Bird Lecture – Territoriality & Song 5/11/93 (#497) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Bird Lecture – Migration, Navigation, & Orientation 5/13/96 (#498) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Global Environ: New Challenges to Intl. Organiz – Kyoto 4/25/93 (#499) (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Hum. Bio Lecture – Protecting Biodiversity 5/24/93 (#500) (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Making Choices in the Research University 6/1/93 (#501) (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Forman Graduation 6/6/93 (#502) (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Ewart Thomas' Retirement 6/9/93 (#503) (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Senior Class Day Talk 6/12/93 (#504) (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Doing Better, Feeling Worse – Western Thoracic Surgical Assoc. 6/25/93 (#505) (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Knight Fellows – Introduction of Mark Reisner 6/29/93 (#506) (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Remarrying Research and Teaching 8/10/93 (#507) (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Sierra Camp – Son of Earth in the Balance… 9/2-9/7/93 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Continuing Studies "Leadership" 10/5/93 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Green Building Dedication 10/21/93 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Center on Conflict and Negotiation "Would We Do It The Same Way Again?" 1/24/94 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Earth Systems Class "Biodiversity" 2/9/94 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Commission on Risk & Risk Management Testimony 2/13/94 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Cal Tech Seminar 2/24/94 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Cornell University "End of Another Century" 4/15/94 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - "Statutory Basis for Risk Assessment" 4/27/94 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Whitman Commencement 5/21/94 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Boething Lecture "Humans, Habitats, & Conservation Policy" 5/24/94 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - "Lead" Lecture 7/20/94 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Sierra Camp Talk Summer 1994 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - AT&T Bell Labs "The Ambivalent University" 9/9/94 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - El Camino Hospital – he Crisis in Health Care: Do We Have One 9/20/94 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Bob Street Farewell 9/29/94 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Coord. Council "The New Reality of Retirement" 10/19/94 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Retreat "Leadership in a Time of Renewal" 11/16/94 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - University Fellows "Managing the New Biology" 12/7/94 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Jack Sheperd Memorial 1/5/95 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Harold Boyd Farewell 1/5/95 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - AAHE Talk "Higher Education: Another Century's End" 1/20/95 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Ethics and Society Lect. "Ethics and the Professoriate" 2/3/95 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Commonwealth Club/AA "What We Don't Teach Our Ph.D.s" 2/22/95 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Stegner Lecture Peninsula Open Space Dist. 2/23/95 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Camp Memorial Lecture Eric Kandel Introduction 5/2/95 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - H&S Employee Appreciation "Humorous Reflections" 3/20/95 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Emory Univ. Bill Chace Inaug. 6/5/95 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Biomed Research Assoc. "Regulating Research in a Democracy" 5/22/95 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Bulow Class "Biodiversity" 5/26/95 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - GSB – Westley Class 5/30/95 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - David Korn Farewell 6/8/95 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Class Day 6/17/95 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Law School Lead Lecture 7/12/95 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Econ. Inst. "Contract on America"8/2/95 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Biodiversity: Going, Going, Gone? 10/12/95 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Biology 2 10/12/95 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Med School Ethics Class 2/15/96 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - A/Parc-Nedo Symposium 2/7/96 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - National Science Board – Davis "The Role and Contrib. of Private Research Universities" 3/28/96 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Welcome Jewish Studies Day 5/14/96 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - U of Wash – Future Faculty: What will it be like? 5/23/96 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Rotary Club Speech 7/8/96 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Health and the Environment – no date (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Basic Research and the American Research Universities 9/1996 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Senior Class Talk 9/1996 (#540) (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Re-engineering the Ph. D. Octopus 10/2/96 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Valuing Nature 2/1997 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Quality Health Care at Low Cost: Can We Have Both? 1/24/97 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Environmental Quality, Security and Global Change – Lawrence Livermore Nat'l. Labs 7/16/97 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - L. Livermore National Lab "Environment & Security" 7/16/97 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Yale 10/1997 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Chocolate Talk 12/98 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Teller Wildlife Refuge – Colorado 7/1999 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Internationalizing/Universalizing the Univ. U of VA 10/15/99 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - What Matters to Me & Why 10/27/99 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Keynote Address: Case Meeting, SF 12/5/99 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Halsell Lecture 2/11/00 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Occidental College (Ted Mitchell Inaug.) 4/10/00 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Stanford Report Faculty Essay 5/31/00 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Cuthbertson Memorial 6/5/00 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Keystone Awards Dinner – Bruce Alberts Introduction 6/13/00 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Incyte: Science First "Science as Communication" 6/21/00 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Stanford Executive Program "The Political Economy of Climate Change" 7/31/00 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - National University – San Diego 9/22/00 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Oak Knoll School 1/20/00 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - AAAS Topical Lecture 2/17/01 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - FORUM/CESP Genome Talk 4/19/01 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Oneonta, New York 10/4/00 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Chicago/FermiLab 6/25/01 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - NPR (Stem Cells) 8/10/01 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Tribute to Leah Kaplan 9/17/01 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - NPR Science Friday 10/19/01 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - The Cohn Lecture – Rockefeller University, NYC 10/1/01 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - AAAS/ New Tests for Science (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - National Conference on Science, Policy & Environment, WDC 12/2001 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - TIGR – WDC 1/17/02 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - WCBR Snowmass 1/26/02 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Op Ed NY Times 1/5/02 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - PEW Scholars, Puerto Vallarta 3/18/02 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Neuroethics, SF 5/13/92 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Bird Song Lecture 5/14/92 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - CISAC Lecture 5/28/92 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Roche/Gunn High School 8/1/02 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - GSB Lecture, Stanford Executive Program 8/5/02 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Shannon Lecture/NIH 11/20/02 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Carnegie Meeting, Palo Alto 11/7/02 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Stanford Healthcare Symposium 1/25/03 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Lecture/Human Bio 2/12/03 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Mt. Sinai Symposium, NYC 3/6/03 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Last Lecture Speaker Series, Stanford Business School 4/8/03 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Parsonnet Course 4/17/03 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Forum/CESP 5/28/03 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Cambridge Talk/Science 6/2003 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Goldsmith Retirement 9/26/03 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Maxine Singer Event 9/24/03 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Society for Neuroscience, New Orleans, LA 11/10/03 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Heinz Board, DC 11/19/03 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Sun Valley Writers Conf. 8/25/04 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - American College of Surgeons, 91st Annual 10/16-10/20/05 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Cubberly Lecture 4/4/07 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - "Covering Science in Cyberspace," Los Angeles 3/11-3/12/07 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Kyoto Prize Gala (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Speech File (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2012-005
  - Letter from Derek Bok, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Letter from President Ford, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Leadership for America: Rebuilding the Public Service, National Commission on the Public Service, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Centennial Symposium: The Info Explosion, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Speech by President of Mexico, 100th anniversary of Stanford, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Address to the Class of 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Law Institute 68th Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Harvard Grad School 100th Anniversary (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Humans in the Chemical Decision Chain", 1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Photos-UK (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Photos-Trip to Taiwan (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Photos (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - News Clippings (Box 1, Folder 13)